<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.scrubsv2" version="5.1.54" name="[COLOR orange]Scrubs v2[/COLOR]" provider-name="JewBMX, [COLOR red]The Red Wizard[/COLOR]">
    <requires>
        <import addon="script.module.six" />
        <import addon="script.module.kodi-six" />
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
        <import addon="script.module.requests" />
        <import addon="script.module.resolveurl" />
        <import addon="script.scrubsv2.artwork" optional="true" />
        <import addon="script.trakt" optional="true" />
        <import addon="plugin.video.youtube" optional="true" />
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="main.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension library="service.py" point="xbmc.service" start="startup" />
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary lang="en">Free and non-Debrid Movies, TV Shows and Anime</summary>
        <description lang="en">Free and non-Debrid Movies, TV Shows and Anime. Additional sources in Tools > Settings > Provider Settings (returning false positives, but they might work depending on your IP address)[CR][CR][COLOR red]Shamelessly forked and updated by The Red Wizard[/COLOR] [COLOR orange]- until JewBMX returns![/COLOR] [COLOR blue]Many thanks to The Alpha![/COLOR]</description>
        <disclaimer lang="en">The author is not responsible for the use of this addon. The author is not responsible for the content found using this addon. The author does not host or own any content found within this addon.[CR]The author is in no way affiliated with Kodi, Team Kodi, or the XBMC Foundation.[CR]This is a Non-profit resource, organized solely for educational purposes which is protected under the Fair-Use doctrine of the Copyright Act, Specifically section 107, which does promote freedom of expression, by permitting the unlicensed use of copyright-protected works.</disclaimer>
        <license>Free the People! Free the World!!</license>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/images/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/images/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
        <news>2026-01-22
- NEW: Existing Changelog now "What's New"
- NEW: Previous [COLOR red]The Red Wizard[/COLOR] and [COLOR orange]JewBMX[/COLOR] Changelogs available online and accessed through the Tools menu
- Scraper domain fix: bstsrs primary mirror reverted to bstsrs.in (temporary issue when previously tested)
- FIX: Misnamed changelog function call which caused an error on first launch/update fixed
- NEW: Scraper Tester inside addon settings - Provider Settings now has "Test ALL Scrapers" and "Test a Single Scraper" buttons that HTTP-probe each provider and show a live report
- NEW: Changelog notification - first launch after an update shows a modal "What's New" dialog the user must dismiss; a persistent "What's New" entry is also shown at the root of the addon menu until opened or dismissed</news>
    </extension>
</addon>
